Yahana Hello, we're
We are The Super Jets!
Yahana Ego-hugging dance challenge
Daiko Yay!
Yahana What do you mean?
We are an internet dance bubble.
I've been in the group for about a year now.
And it's been about a year.
We've been making videos for about a year now.
We can at least dance without sound.
Omitsu No, you can do it.
Yahana So...
So, one by one, we're going to have the dancers dance here.
I'll have them dance right here.
I'm going to have them dance here, one at a time.
And then we'll compare them.
That's why.
It's really cool to see all the dancers in sync even in silence.
or "It's so cool!
Or is it cool?
Omitsu No, no, no, no, no, no.
Yabana, no!
Rinne, Daishin, what's your enthusiasm?
Daiko, me?
RinNing, you want that?
Daiko, you haven't shown many dance videos.
RinNing, that's right.
Daiko, it's your first time!
Daiko, at the dumpling place...
Daiko, we were making a TikTok video.
Daiko, how do you make your own TikTok videos?
Omitsu, do you know how to make a TikTok video?
Do you think they didn't have one?
Rin-ning No.
Daiko First time
Rin-ning, no.
Ohmitsu, I've never made a dance video before.
Ohko, you're right.
Ohmitsu, dance practices aren't the same yet.
Ohmitsu It's silent, too.
Ohmitsu That's why this one would probably be different if I had made a dance video.
Yahana Indeed.
Yahana Who seems the most confident?
Ohmitsu Rinnei.
Ohko...
RinNei Ohmitsu
RinNei Ohmitsu, you're confident, aren't you?
Ohmitsu
Ohko, I want to see Yabana dance.
Oh, I'm confident.
Ohko, you're working hard.
Yahana, you know, people who used to do music...
Omitsu Really?
Really? Omitsu, because it makes sense.
Oh, wow.
Oh, wow. - Oh, wow. - Oh, wow.
Omitsu, can we go to a sunny inn?
Oh, wow.
Ohko, don't try to sleep.
Oh, come on, Omitsu.
Omitsu, if you go to bed, who are you?
No, but...
Yahana, the teacher was really pissed at me when I was doing Peyoung.
Yahana.
Omitsu, what's he for if you go to bed?
Yahana, go to sleep.
Ohmitsu, you're laughing.
Omitsu Laughing
Ohmitsu, this is a different fast-paced song.
Omitsu Yes.
Omitsu Oh, there?
Oh, that's it? Oh, no, no, I think it's still pretty tough.
Omitsu The one who was the most out of tune.
Omitsu Let's get angry a lot!
Ohmitsu, by the way, it's not a seven-lacquered word, so there's no blurriness.
Reia, that's right.
Reina, if you start saying that, it's the end.
Ohmitsu No, you're the first to say it.
Daiko So, first of all, let's start with a little example.
Reia, yes.Reina Yes
Ohmitsu Well, we're going to line up and dance once, so you can see what it's like.
Ohmitsu, please see how it's like.
Reia, let's dance!
Let's dance!
Come on, Reia, let's go for it!
Let's go for it, Omitsu!
Ohmitsu Oh!
Yabana, please listen.
Omitsu, square!
Omitsu, one, two.
Omitsu, one, two, three, four.
They're matching.
Whoo!
good night!
by H.
Shintaro.
Shintaro I swung it wrong a few times.
Shintaro. When it's all together, it looks like this.
Yes, sir.
Okay, Shintaro, who's in order now?
Shintaro, number one, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Okay.
Shintaro, with your momentum, Zion Auto Lead, put your enthusiasm in the center.
Shintaro, I'm going to win for sure!
Okay.
Shintaro, let's start with Yuille first.
Shintaro, let's go.
Yuille, I'm off.
Yuille, yes, I'm Yuille for now.
Yuille, I'm very, very anxious to tell you that I'm going to be the first one to perform, and I want to lead you all.
Yooil As the first performer, I'd like to give a performance that will lead you all.
Yoo-il, thank you very much for your cooperation.
Okay, that's all for today.
Thank you very much.
I'm not sure about my enthusiasm, but I'll do my best.
How's it going?
How is it?
Did I do well?
It's my turn.
I'm a little bit alone.
But I'll do my best.
I guess I'll start from here.
Thank you for watching.
Yes, it's my turn now. Well, well, well, I am the oldest, so I will do my best with a little leeway.
I'm the oldest, so I'm going to do my best with a little bit of leeway.
Matsuda: Not perfect, is it?
Matsuda: Yes! Yuki Matsumoto
Matsuda: This time, yes.
Matsuda I'd love to make a tiggle-hug without sound!
Matsuda I'd like to make it happen!
Matsuda Okay, here we go.
One, two, three, four.
Yay!
That's it!
Okay, so, the sixth one...
Well, I'm not so sure about it.
I'll do my best.
Let's go!
See you next time!
See you soon!
Yes, this is Suzuki from Grape. I'm going to take a different face this time, but I'll dance with all my might. Please do!
" square.
" To, to, to. Yay, yay, yay.
" Hi, hi, hi, hi, yay, yay!
" Tsutsu
" with the tererrekimembochi.
" That's great, isn't it?
" chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp.

Thank you!
The other day, Nichi-kun, you all danced at the Moon.
We danced, didn't we?
I heard that a video of you transforming has arrived.
Let's take a look at it.
Let's take a look now!
At first, we were all together, of course.It's all there at the beginning, of course.
That's nice.
Oh, nice.
There's still sound.
We have sound.
There's a sound.
A little better sound faster
That's where we start.
Is it gone? Here.
Okay, good luck.
One more to go.
A few more.
Oh, wow.
That's really good.
That's a good turn.
You're so fast.
You're fast, Yuukiku.
So fast.
You're fast.
Very fast.
You're so fast!
Amazing!
That was crazy!
Is he moving fast?
Oh, wow!
Is it working?
Is it falling?
Oh, yeah.
Ahhh...
Come on, man.
Jesse, you and I are the best.
What?
I'm with you.
Weak, huh?
Yeah, I am.
My feet were lower than yours.
Hey, I'm on the bottom.
Hey, I'm slow, aren't I?
Oh, that's slow.
I'm not slow at all.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's good
I love it, I love it, I love it
Abe great
Abe great, Abe great, Abe great
Abey!
Tommy, no, Abe's great!
Kazuma, what? Abe's amazing.
Tommy, isn't it amazing?
Kazuma, can you hear me? This.
Kazuma, that's amazing.
I'm catching up again.
Look!
Yes! I did it!
I fit right in.
Strong-willed in an ant's body.
Oh, my God.
Quick, quick, quick!
Oh, my God!
I'm so bad!
I'm more finished than I thought I'd be.
I'm done.
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
But I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
I could take it slow.
Oh, they got it.
Almost there!
More, more, more!
Wow! Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God! Oh, my gosh!
Yeah!
The results are in!
Kaito Miyachika wins!
Seventh place!
Oh, 6th place?
Oh, I see.Oh, right.
Sixth place.
Gyuul!
Minus 5.48.
That was quick.
Finished early.
Next 5th place
Yuki
Minus 5.35
The next fourth place goes to
PERCURE
minus 3.5
Next in third place
Harumin
Class already here
1.63
too close to call
Second place goes to Gachu Axessar
plus 0.94
very close
That was close.
The rest
There are two left.
Oh, my God.
You're in first place.
Which is it?
Seventh place goes to...
Pen!
[Snap!
Salt!
Eeeee!
Everyone's record is minus 10 points!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Minus 2 points
Ehhhh!
That's impossible.
Double it.
Ten.
He threw himself off.
Oh, my God.
You want me to match you up?
Yes, I do.
And the first place goes to...
I'll take that as a no. 1.
Oh, my God!
No discrepancies.
Eeeeeeeee!
Something happened during the contest, and it was kind of fast.
I don't know how it got faster, but they fixed it.
The chorus part is really sharp!
If we didn't cut out the chorus, it would probably be out of tune.
You're going to do 10 seconds here?
Oh, man.
We're done.
I'm so happy.
That's great. That's really great.
Applause.
Kaito Miyachika: Seriously, not even a second.
Known for her great talent, Kyoeru Kawashima, that's amazing!
Miyachika Kaito It was a different day this time, but...
Miyachika Kaito Next time... there are many levels of stupidity to defy.
Kaito Miyachika: I'd like to challenge this one too.
Nyoru Kawashima That sounds great!
Kaito Miyachika Well, please look forward to the next time.
Nakamura Kaito See you next time
Nakamura Kaito Revenge!
KAWASHIMA JOETHERU That's all for now.
That's all for The Super Less!
Bye bye!
From Kaito Miyachika
Oh, it's just me!
What's up?
It's okay!